Brandon Mazikowski

Software Engineer

San Jose, CA

408-857-1993 email me linkedin portfolio

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 12+ years experience in customer service. Natural ability to promote products and build rapport through listening and communication skills. Well rounded individual in oral communication and experience with working in groups. Energetic self-starter with strong communication skills; work well independently or on a team. Ambitious, flexible team member who loves to learn. Skilled problem-solver and multi-tasker.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native, NodeJS, MongoDB/Mongoose, Express, SQL, MySQL, Ruby, and Ruby on Rails, JQuery, Python, Javascript, Figma, Bootstrap.

PROJECTS

Storefront app - Mongoose, Express, Node, jQuery and Bootstrap.

The next Yelp app - MERN stack with one other developer.

First todo - Ruby and React with 3 other developers

Wallpaper - React Native.

WaterCooler - MERN stack with 3 other developers and a UX/UI team.

Created full-stack web applications, using recursive algorithms and web forms.
Leveraged debugging strategies to ensure program integrity. Plan, wrote, tested, deployed and launched full-stack applications. Leveraged third-party APIs and integrated them into websites and applications. Developed a portfolio of individual and collaboratively built projects

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly: Online immersive software engineer course

February 2019 - June 2020

Worked on projects, homework, and studied 12 to 14 hour a day Monday through Sunday.
Worked with a study group every day, helping each other bug hunt and solve algorithms.
Completed the 420 hour software engineer course.

Deputy Sheriff: Santa Clara County Sheriff - Santa Clara, CA

February 2019 - June 2020

• Team environment made the job possible. Able to complete tasks with limited instruction. Always studied to stay up to speed on the latest laws. Pushed day in and day out to become better. Communicated with colleagues to see if they needed help.

Fitness Coach: Mint condition Fitness - Los Gatos, CA

February 2017-2018

• Being able to multitask throughout the whole day. Manage client's scheduling and their workout routine. Stayed up to date with new certifications by studying and taking tests. Team environment, taking on other trainers clients when needed. Worked six days a week.

Brandon's Cross Fitness Training: Los Gatos/Gilroy, CA

February 2007-2016

• In control of my own schedule, and managed time very well. Being able to communicate with people very well. Worked with other independent trainers. Able to acquire and maintain clientele.

EDUCATION

General Assembly - Online 2020 to 2021

Software Engineer

Gavilan College- Gilroy, CA 2012 to 2016

Graduated with AA in kinesiology sports medicine

West Valley College -Saratoga, CA 2001-2004

Graduated with AA in communications/Liberal arts